<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hash Map on Jackson的博客</title><link>http://localhost:1414/tags/hash-map/</link><description>Recent content in Hash Map on Jackson的博客</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.2</generator><language>zh-TW</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:21:27 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1414/tags/hash-map/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[Leetcode] Find Original Array From Doubled Array(Medium)</title><link>http://localhost:1414/leetcodes/leetcode2007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:21:27 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1414/leetcodes/leetcode2007/</guid><description>LeetCode 2007 - Find Original Array From Doubled Array An integer array original is transformed into a doubled array changed by appending twice the value of every element in original, and then randomly shuffling the resulting array. Given an array changed, return original if changed is a doubled array. If changed is not a doubled array, return an empty array. The elements in original may be returned in any order.</description></item><item><title>[Leetcode] Create Binary Tree From Descriptions(Medium)</title><link>http://localhost:1414/leetcodes/leetcode442/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 22:02:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1414/leetcodes/leetcode442/</guid><description>LeetCode 442 - Find All Duplicates in an Array Given an integer array nums of length n where all the integers of nums are in the range [1, n] and each integer appears once or twice, return an array of all the integers that appears twice. You must write an algorithm that runs in O(n) time and uses only constant extra space. example Input: nums = [4,3,2,7,8,2,3,1] Output: [2,3] Input:</description></item><item><title>[Leetcode] Create Binary Tree From Descriptions(Medium)</title><link>http://localhost:1414/leetcodes/leetcode2196/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 21:45:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1414/leetcodes/leetcode2196/</guid><description>LeetCode 2196 - Create Binary Tree From Descriptions You are given a 2D integer array descriptions where descriptions[i] = [parenti, childi, isLefti] indicates that parenti is the parent of childi in a binary tree of unique values. Furthermore, If isLefti == 1, then childi is the left child of parenti. If isLefti == 0, then childi is the right child of parenti. Construct the binary tree described by descriptions and</description></item></channel></rss>